Well, I think
it's going to
be the next
major computing platform.
So if you
look at the
grand arc of
computing over time,
you've gone from
mainframes to
computers that
basically live on
your desk or
on a tower,
to phones that
you have in
your hand that
you basically can
take with you
everywhere that you
want, but it's
pretty unnatural.
It takes you
away from the
world around you.
And I think
that the trend
in computing is
it gets more
ubiquitous, it gets
more natural, and
it just gets
more social.
So you want
to be able
to interact with
people in the
world around you,
and I think
that this is
probably going to
be the next
major platform after
phones. I'll give
these to you.
These are the
clear ones that
show all the
Yeah, the whole
thing is a
special edition, and
this is a
really special edition.
There's not a
single millimeter